<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>Skillbooker.com</title>
<link>http://Skillbooker.com</link>
<description>Jobs, Freelance Projects, Tutorials</description>
<language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>Java Developer Position - Oxford - Energy Market</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/java-developer-position-oxford-energy-market__1543151327</link>
    <description>As a new and exciting business start-up, they are already experiencing a lot of demand and are in need for 2x Java Developers to come on board and work alongside the modelling team to allow clients to be able to access their data/ services remotely.rnrn rnrnAs a successful applicant you would be responsible for developing applications that will majorly influence decisions in the energy sector. phprnrn rnrnThe key responsibilities include:rnrn  Design, build and test the software developed by this company using high resolution energy market simulation softwarernrn  Working with the full SDLC.rnrn  Prepare and install solutions be designing specifications and programming.rnrn  Collaborate with the team to brainstorm and create new products rnrnThe main technical requirements they are looking for:rnrn  Javarnrn  Relational databases  SQL etc.rnrn  Application of lifecycle managementrnrn  RESTful web services rnrn  AWS PHPrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Basingstoke</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-basingstoke__1543151327</link>
    <description>Job Description:rnrn rnrn  Improving functionality and building new features for existing web applicationsrnrn  Designing, building and supporting high-quality, complex web applications to support the work of the organisationrnrn  Liaising with internal and external stakeholders to document features and requirementsrnrn  Provide support for a collection of CMS websitesrnrn rnrnEssential Skills:rnrn rnrn  JavaScriptrnrn  PHPrnrn  Experience working with GIT / SVNrnrn rnrnDesirable Skills:rnrn rnrn  RESTful API srnrn  Experience working with JavaScript frameworks and libraries e.g. Angular, D3rnrn  Experience of working with WordPressrnrn rnrnSalary/Benefits:rnrn rnrn  Work from home 1 day a weekrnrn  35 hour weekrnrn  Flexible workings hoursrnrn  Up to 35krnrn  Pensionrnrn  Healthcarern</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Symfony Project - Work From Home</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/symfony-project-work-from-home__1543151327</link>
    <description>Whether you re more Front End focused or you re a solid Back End Developer, I would like to hear from you if you have Symfony experience.rnrnThere is plenty of scope to work remotely from home each week. The project is for 3 months. Day rate is up to 400 a day depending on experience.rnrnrnExperience in the following is required:rn rnrn	Symfonyrn	HTML 5rn	CSS 3rn	Javascript/jQueryrnrnrn </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Angular 2+ Contract-Reigate</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/angular-2-contract-reigate__1543151327</link>
    <description>Angular 2+ (18 months-24 months commercial experience)rnrnGood communicationrnrn rnrnThe project you ll be working on will be 3 projects spread across and for one of the projects you will need to interact with the other developers.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Nottingham</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-nottingham__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - We are actively seeking a PHP Developer to join a major Legal Research Company based in Nottingham for an initial 6 months. As the PHP Developer you will be bank-end service and API focussed working on highly scalable data supply services hosted in AWS.rnrnThe PHP Developer will need a passion for technology and enjoys working in a collective environment. The PHP Developer will need solid experience working with Object-Orientated PHP using LAMP stack. The PHP Developer will previously have worked in an Agile environment using TDD. The PHP Developer should be dynamic and not be afraid to get involved!rnrnKey skills for the PHP Developer:rnrnrn	Solid experience working with PHP7 and OOPHP.rn	LAMP and AWS.rn	Worked with TDD.rn	Dynamic and a passion for technology.rn	Excellent communication skills are vital.rnrnrnPHP DeveloperrnLocation: NottinghamrnDuration: 6 months initialrnDay Rate: 500 - 550rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer London</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-london__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer required!rnrnAn expert in PHP is required for a huge client of ours, based in central London. The PHP developer will be working in a cross functional Agile team, delivering high quality tested code. As an expert in PHP, you have to understand OOP and have commercial experience testing your code. The PHP developer will work with a huge online based company that are market leaders in their field.rnrnPHP Developer requirements:rnrn* Strong working knowledge of PHPrn* Understanding of OOPrn* JavaScriptrn* TDD/BDDrn* Good CSS and design principlesrn* Good database knowledge (MySQL)rnrnI m almost certain that you would have heard of this company, and they will definitely stand out on your CV. It s a great opportunity to earn a great day rate, in a fantastic environment on a 6-month contract (with the chance to extend). If you think you know PHP inside out, comfortable working in a fast-paced dynamic team and want a challenge, this is the role for you.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer - Drupal</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-drupal__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - Drupal rnLondon rn 450pd - 500pdrnrnPHP Developer (Drupal) required!rnrnAn experienced PHP Developer, with extensive use of Drupal 8 is needed for a huge client of ours, based in London. The PHP Developer will be working in a TDD environment in a very senior team of developers. As one of the senior PHP Developers, you ll need a solid grounding in various areas of tech.rnrnPHP Developer (Drupal) requirements:rnrn* Drupal 8rn* PHP Developmentrn* MVC Frameworks (Symfony)rn* Unit Testing/BDD/TDDrn* Dockerrn* MySQLrnrnThis is a great contract, initially for 3 months with the view to extend. You would have definitely heard of the client, and they would look great on your CV. If you feel you have good CMS experience, as well as hands on coding with PHP, then please apply.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Colchester, Essex</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-colchester-essex__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer based in Essex | Excellent opportunityrnrnWe have an opportunity for a PHP Developer to join an expanding company. As the PHP Developer you will be working alongside a team of fast paced and dynamic individuals on a variety of projects at any one time.rnrnDo you have?rnrn* Excellent experience of PHP developmentrn* Strong experience of developing in WordPressrn* Experience with MVC frameworks, Cake PHP would be idealrn* Familiar with the SQL Server databasern* Passion for the drive to develop new ideas and use new technologyrn* Experience of working within a Linux environmentrnrnDo you want to?rnrn* Work for fast progressing companyrn* Be rewarded financiallyrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Suffolk</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-suffolk__1543151328</link>
    <description>We have an opportunity for a PHP Developer to join an expanding company. As the PHP Developer you will be working alongside a team of fast paced and dynamic individuals on a variety of projects at any one time.rnrnDo you have? rnrn* Excellent experience of PHP developmentrn* Strong experience of developing in WordPressrn* Experience with MVC frameworks, CakePHP would be idealrn* Familiar with the SQL Server databasern* Passion for the drive to develop new ideas and use new technologyrn* Experience of working within a Linux environmentrnrnDo you want to?rnrn* Work for fast progressing companyrn* Be rewarded financially rn </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer, Software Engineer, MySQL, Agile, TDD</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-software-engineer-mysql-agile-tdd__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer, Software Engineer, MySQL, Agile, TDDrnrnOur global client and innovative client are seeking a talented PHP Developer/Software Engineer to join one of their Nottingham based teams. The Software Engineer must have a strong background in PHP. The successful Software Engineer will be working within a highly agile team, supporting multiple products and offers a great opportunity for PHP Developer/Software Engineer to contribute significantly to the success of the company.rnrnMain Responsibilities of PHP Developer/Software Engineer:rnrnrn	To provide all round solution design, development and diagnostic services using modern PHP frameworks and technologies for our web applications, web service solutions and batch processing servicesrn	To provide technical leadership to our cross-functional agile product development teamsrn	Work closely with product and project management to deliver timely products and enhancementsrnrnrnThe PHP Developer/Software Engineer will bring skills in:rnrnrn	Extensive PHP development skills using modern PHP frameworks, grounded in PHP-FIG PSRsrn	Working experience in Kanban or scrumrn	Good understanding of modern development Build, Test and Deployment pipelinesrn	Experience working with Relational databasesrn	Excellent oral and written communication skills with a customer-centric approachrn	A strong understanding of SOA and API concepts, including securityrn	A strong working knowledge of application development tools and methodologiesrnrnrnThe PHP Developer/Software Engineer will ideally bring skills in:rnrnrn	Experience of querying distributed data platforms and data warehousesrn	Experience of TDD for contributing to automated test packsrn	Active participation in the development communityrn	Experience of MV* Front End frameworksrn	Practical experience of message queuing systemsrn	rn	This is a great opportunity for a PHP developer to join an excellent team. This role is based in Nottingham and highly commutable from Derby, Loughborough, Mansfield, Burton etc.rnrn	PHP Developer, Software Engineer, MySQL, Agile, TDDrnrn	Referral Scheme: If this role isn t for you then perhaps you could recommend a friend or colleague to Haybrook IT. If we go on to place that person in a permanent or temporary capacity then you could be rewarded with 500! Please see our website for terms and conditions.rnrn	Haybrook IT Resourcing is Oxford s leading IT recruitment agency. With exclusive access to some of the region s most successful companies, send in your CV today to secure your next IT position.rnrn	Haybrook IT Resourcing Ltd acts as an employment agency and an employment business.rnrn	We value diversity and always appoint on merit.rn	rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP/Laravel Developer - £250-£325 MANCHESTER LIVERPOOL LANCASHIRE</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/phplaravel-developer-a250-a325-manchester-liverpool-lancashire__1543151328</link>
    <description>Manchester they boast some huge clients including house hold names. With a modern office space and an agency work- life balance this an opportunity not to be missed. Most contractors I have spoke with in recent times complain about the same issues, companies expecting more from them because they aren t a permanent employee. Fortunately I have been working with this client exclusively for some time, my client treat contractors the same and often look to bring the contractors back when their contracts finish.rnrnMy client are looking for an energetic PHP Developer to join them on a 6 month contract with a view to continued extentions. They would ideally like the developer to start ASAP but are willing to wait for the right candidate. The daily rate on offer is between 250- 325 which provides an opportunity for junior- mid level developers to join the contract world or continue their contract career.rnrnInterview s are happening as early as the week and thye are keen to make a decision as soon as the right candidate applies so get in touch today if you d like to hear more.rnrnThe skills required for the role?rnrnrn	PHP (4,5  6)rn	Laravelrn	JavascriptrnrnrnMy client would ideally like someone with Craft CMS however they are willing to bring the contractor up to speed with this if the PHP Developer does not already have this skill. There aren t many companies in today s amrket that are willing to train contractors onsite.rnrnIf this opportunity is of interest to you call me directly on: (see below).rnrnOr email me your CV: (see below)rnrnPearson Frank International is the leading Java/PHP recruitment firm in the UK, advertising more JAVA  PHP jobs than any other agency. We deal with both Digital Agencies  End Users throughout the UK and Europe and we have never had more live requirements  Web Development jobs for JAVA  PHP professionals. By specialising solely in placing candidates in the JAVA  PHP market I have built relationships with most of the key employers in the UK and have an unrivalled understanding of where the best opportunities  JAVA/PHP jobs are.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Surrey </title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-surrey__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer (LAMP Stack) - Surrey - ContractrnrnAvanti s Key client based in Surrey are actively searching for PHP developers to join their team to build web applications using PHP (LAMP Stack) during an incredibly busy and fruitful time for their organisation.rnrnA keen eye to detail and Back End experience is a MUSTrnrnDuties and responsibilities include but are not limited to:rnrnrn	PHP programming, enhancements, bug fixes, modifications, and additions to the Back Office systemrn	Data management and reporting using MySQLrn	Customer support and troubleshooting managementrn	Server and Service management on Azure platformsrnrnrnEssential experience includes:rnrnrn	PHPrn	JavaScript with jQueryrn	MySQLrn	Full knowledge of HTML and CSSrnrnrnThis is for an initial 3 month contract with the strong possibility to extend due to the volume of work to be carried out.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer | Guildford | 3 - 6 Month | Laravel </title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-guildford-3-6-month-laravel__1543151328</link>
    <description>An expert PHP developer is needed for a client of mine in Guildford. The client work extensively in the marketing sector. The successful candidate will be working in a exciting team of other senior developers with the possibility of mentoring a junior developer. rnrnThe essential skills required are:rnrn	Commemrcial experience using Laravel (Symfony would also be beneficial)rn	TDD or BDDrn	Strong team working skillsrn	MySQLrnrnWhat makes you standout:rnrnrn	Experience of using Vue.jsrn	Able to write API srn	History of working in digital agencies.rnrnIf you think you would be a good for this role and are looking for a challenge, please send over an updated CV, and I will be in touch with you. The client are looking to carry out telephone interviews next week - so be quick!</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer - Laravel</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-laravel__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - Laravel - LondonrnrnOur client is looking for a PHP Developer to be involved with development and enhancements to PHP applications. You will be part of a small team for this potentially long-term contract.rnrnYou will need a blend of the following skills:rnrnPHP DevelopmentrnrnPHP Frameworks - LaravelrnrnMySQLrnrnIf you are looking for a new PHP contract please forward your CVrnrn rnrnDue to the volume of applications received for positions, it will not be possible to respond to all applications and only applicants who are considered suitable for interview will be contacted.rnrnProactive Appointments Limited operates as an employment agency and employment business and is an equal opportunities organisationrnrnWe take our obligations to protect your personal data very seriously. Any information provided to us will be processed as detailed in our Privacy Notice, a copy of which can be found on our websitern</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Basingstoke</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-basingstoke__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - Zend, HTML, JavaScript, MVC - BasingstokernrnYour Role:rnrnAs the PHP Developer you will be a major contributor to the development team, working on the design, build and tests to growing web-based products and services, including one of the UK leading mobile parking solutions. You will make a major impact on the developments of a number of key products, which may also add new skills to your portfolio.rnrnSome of the key activities you will be involved in will include;rnrnrn	You will bring a creative but practical approach to the programming and technical development of the key products and services.rn	Also you will be involved in the deployment of all web-based solutions on the Application Service Platformrn	Part of your role will include post production support,rnrnrnA bit about you;rnrnYou will be an experienced PHP Developer, with skills and experience including;rnrnrn	Knowledge of PHP Frameworks, for example; Zend or Codeignitorrn	Experience of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and Ajaxrn	Knowledge of MySQL or SQL Serverrn	Previous experience of developing in a Windows/Linux environmentrn	Knowledge of administering Apache would be advantageousrn	Experience of GIT and SVN would be beneficialrnrnrn rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Peterborough, Cambridgeshire - £375-£400 a Day</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-peterborough-cambridgeshire-a375-a400-a-day__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP developer with Symfony experience working for an online insurance broker.rnrnYou will be a crucial element in launching their product in 80 new countries!rnrnThe product will help provide commercial and residential properties all around the glob and even offer legal advice.rnrnThis is a 6-month contract starting as soon as possible!rnrnYou will be working on several projects for my client all focused around PHP and Symfony.rnrnSkills Requiredrnrnrn	PHPrn	MySQLrn	HTMLrn	Symfony 3 and abovern	jQueryrn	CSSrn	JavaScriptrnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer - Laravel - Swindon</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-laravel-swindon__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP contractor developer required!rnrnImmediate start.rnrnAn experienced PHP developer required. The contract is initially 6 months, with a view to extending. The role is working with a market leading software platform. You will be working with a highly skilled team, producing high levels of quality code. You will need to have several years of experience primarily focusing on Back End PHP development, ideally using the Laravel framework, Symfony or Zend (not essential).rnrnPrevious experience:rnrnrn	Self starterrn	Several years experience coding with PHPrn	Experience writing RESTful APIsrn	Working in an agile team environmentsrn	Experience working with microservices based web appsrn	Experience using containerisation such as Docker or Kubernetes (not essential, but positive)rnrnrnIf this is of interest to yourself please apply now.rnrnPHP, Laravel, Docker/Kubernetesrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Northampton, Northamptonshire</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-northampton-northamptonshire__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - Northampton - DOErnrnYou must have experience of PHP, as part of your degree with a years minimum experience, with good communication skills.rnrnRole involves development of reliable, efficient and user friendly software and products including user documentation, to industry standard procedure and methods, as part of a structured team of Developers.rnrnYou d be joining a sociable team who are very collaborative, as such this role requires someone who thrives in this sort of environment, a desire to learn will also get you a long way here.rnrnEssential Skills (as with 1-3 years min. experience)rnrnrn	rn	PHPrn	rn	rn	JavaScriptrn	rn	rn	HTML/CSSrn	rnrnrnSecondary Skillsrnrnrn	rn	RestfulAPIsrn	rn	rn	ERP Knowledgern	rn	rn	Agile Methodology/Scrum experiencern	rn	rn	Source Controlrn	rn	rn	Coding Standardsrn	rnrnrnSoft Skillsrnrnrn	rn	Excellent interpersonal skillsrn	rn	rn	Clear communicatorrn	rn	rn	Brings new ideas and ways of working in order to achieve better resultsrn	rn	rn	Thrives working in teamsrn	rn	rn	Be enthusiastic and motivated to drive change through technologyrn	rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Nottingham</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-nottingham__1543151328</link>
    <description>The successful candidate will have the following experience: rnrnExcellent knowledge of PHP programming and excellent Back End experience. rnStrong track-record of development projects using LAMP stack rnMySQL experience rnExperience of TDD and the use of automated testing rnFamiliarity of PHP Composer, Packagist or experience building systems for AWS hosting environments would be advantageous rnGood understanding of GIT rnExperienced in Agile methodology, sprints, stand-ups etc rnExcellent team worker, able to work collaboratively in a tight knit, innovative and friendly team</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer Manchester</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-manchester__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP DeveloperrnrnOne of our large clients is looking to recruit a PHP Developer based in Manchester;rnrnSkills/Experiencernrnrn	Develop object-oriented code in PHP that promotes reuse, readability, and best-practice coding standardsrn	Participate in the full development life cycle including, architecture, design, development and testingrn	Participate in Scrum ceremoniesrn	Peer review other developers codern	Work closely with and incorporate feedback from other engineersrn	Work with other developers to share your skills and proficiencyrn	Experience with OO PHP (non-framework based)rn	Experience with version control systems ( eg git)rn	Experience with Linux or another UNIX OSrn	Experience with tools such as PHPUnitrn	Creation of functional and unit tests with industry standardrnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Front End Developer Required - Highworth, Swindon - 35k</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/front-end-developer-required-highworth-swindon-35k__1543151328</link>
    <description>My client specialize in offering marketing solutions to their many clients across many sectors, property and finance to name a couple, including property portal and oxford railings. They have grown exponentially over the last 12 months, and are looking to grow their development team from 5 to 10 over the coming months. They are looking for a front end developer to come in and work on creating bespoke web apps and websites for their clients marketing campaigns.rnrn rnrnIn terms of skillset, they are looking for a developer with experience with the following:rnrn rnrnrn	HTML5rn	CSS3rn	JavaScriptrn	JQueryrn	Angular JS (Nice to have)rn	UX/UI Design (Nice to have)rnrnrn rnrnThey are looking for a developer who is capable of working on multiple different projects at one time, and someone with at least 2 years commercial experience.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Work from Home Front End Developer needed</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/work-from-home-front-end-developer-needed__1543151328</link>
    <description>A great client of mine based in West Sussex is on the look out for a Front End Developer with Drupal or Symfony experience for an initial 6 month contract with the view to extend.  350pdayrn rnPlease note you can work from home (1st week onsite to get to grips with the project) then a maximum of 1 day a week onsite.rn rnKey Skillsrnrn	Javascriptrn	Angularrn	Drupal or Symfonyrn	Twigrn	 rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Urgent Role - PHP Developer - Contract - London</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/urgent-role-php-developer-contract-london__1543151328</link>
    <description>I am recruiting for an PHP Developer to join a well-established client of ours on a 4 month contract basis based in London rnrnJob Title: PHP Developer.rnrnLocation: LondonrnrnContract Length: 4 months rnrnDay rate: 200  300 (There is flexibility to increase the rate so let me know what you d need)rnrnStart date: As soon as possiblern</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP - Contract - Manchester</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-contract-manchester__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer rnrnCommercialsrnLength: 3 Months with Extension LikelyrnLocation: Manchester City CentrernRate: FlexiblernStart Date: ASAP rn rnOverviewrnrnMy Client is looking for a PHP developer who has a history of working on or building API s or REST to build and design one for a react website. This will be part of a continuous platform project so extensions will be likely.rnrnThis shall includide using an active rapper system to pull in - the Headless CMS is consentful / Jss, Foreign Platform, Algolia ServicernrnSkills Requiredrnrnrn	PHP, cakePHP, MySQLrn	API s, REST experiencern	React experience (Non-essential)rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>PHP Developer - Swindon - 6 month contract - Market Rate</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-swindon-6-month-contract-market-rate__1543151328</link>
    <description>PHP Developer - Swindon - 6 month contract - Market RaternrnrnThe perfect developer for the role will have the following skills under their belt:rnrnKey Skills:rnrnrn	rn	PHP  Laravel ideally; but Symfony / Zend is also acceptable﻿rn	rn	rn	Agile Working Experiencern	rnrnrnDesired Skills:rnrnrn	rn	Writing API srn	rn	rn	Working with microservices based web appsrn	rn	rn	Experience working﻿ with Angularrn	rn	rn	DevOps Knowledge: Docker / Kubernetesrn	rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Full Stack Symfony Developer – Ross-on-Wye (Part Remote Working) – Rate DOE</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/full-stack-symfony-developer-a-ross-on-wye-part-remote-working-a-rate-doe__1543151328</link>
    <description>This one is looking to be a 6 month initial contract.rnrn rnrnThe client are based in Ross-on-Wye  and they appreciate that they are not the most accessible, so will be happy to accept 2 days on site/ 3 days remote working.rnrn rnrnThe main website is built on a Symfony / Doctrine framework, and this project will involve dealing with Legacy Systems. The developer will hopefully be a Full Stack Developer  with experience of Symfony and JavaScript / HTML / CSS.rnrnKey Skills:rnrnrn	rn	PHPrn	rn	rn	Symfonyrn	rn	rn	LAMP Stackrn	rn	rn	Git (Git implementation uses GITFLOW)rn	rn	rn	JavaScript, HTML  CSSrn	rnrnrn rnrnDesired Skills:rnrnrn	rn	jQueryrn	rn	rn	RESTful API srn	rn	rn	Bootstrap / SASSrn	rn	rn	MariaDBrn	rn	rn	.Twig Page Templatesrn	rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Magento Contract | Guildford | 2-3 Month Contract</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/magento-contract-guildford-2-3-month-contract__1543151328</link>
    <description>This particular role is for an experienced Magento developer who is confident and can hit the ground running. The Magento developer will need to be comfortable working with Magento 2 and be able to collaborate with the in-house frontend developerrnrnMagento Developer Requirements:rnrnrn	rn	Commercial experience with Magento 2rn	rn	rn	Magento Certifiedrn	rn	rn	Ability to hit the ground running!rn	rn	rn	Good understanding of backend technologiesrn	rnrnrnThe end client are looking to start interviews this week with a possible start date of next week. This role will be paying 150 - 175 per day depending on experience.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>JavaScript React Contract- Beaconsfield</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/javascript-react-contract-beaconsfield__1543151328</link>
    <description>They are looking to add a JavaScript/ React Web Developer to deliver ground breaking new web applications for their clients.rnrnKey skills:rnrnJavaScriptrnrnReactrnrnSQL DatabasesrnrnDealing with complex data structures and schemasrnrnWorking in a test-driven mannerrnrnGitrnrnGit/GitHubrnrnAgilernrnSOAPrnrnREST APIsrnrnDesired skills:rnrnReact NativernrnGraphQLrnrnThis will be for 6 months and is looking to pay between 500- 550 per day.rnrnThey are looking to get someone started ASAP so if you re interested please send your most updated CV and get in touch on the details below.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lead Developer - PERMANENT!</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/lead-developer-permanent__1543151328</link>
    <description>Roc Search are in the process of recruiting a Lead DeveloperrnrnThe Lead developer role at stage 3 of engine room process will be responsible for the technical design, development and testing of the company s expanding suite of software products and maintaining the software on an ongoing basis. You will be responsible for team of developers ensuring on-time, quality and budget targets are met.rnrn rnrnYou will also lead a small team across data including one developer and one junior team member.rnrnExperience rnrnrn	JavaScriptrn	JQueryrn	Androidrn	IOSrn	HTML / CSSrn	SQLrn	Good troubleshooting skills and the ability to write clean, easy to maintain codernrnrn rnrnDesirablernrnrn	Linux/Unix scriptingrn	Agile or Waterfallrn	MySQL rnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lydney contract - php - 6 months</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/lydney-contract-php-6-months__1544727132</link>
    <description>I m currently resourcing for a contract software developer role for a company based in Lydney. They are looking to bring someone on board for an initial 6 month period. They are looking to pay between 250 and 300 per day.rnrnKey Skills:rnrnrn	rn	PHPrn	rn	rn	MySQLrn	rn	rn	HTMLrn	rn	rn	CSSrn	rn	rn	JavaScriptrn	rn	rn	jQueryrn	rn	rn	Git / Source Controlrn	rnrnrnDesirable Skills:rnrnrn	rn	Knowledge of IIS / Apachern	rn	rn	Linux / command linern	rn	rn	Bootstrap 3rn	rn	rn	MS-SQLrn	rn	rn	PDOrn	rnrnrnYou will be working within a close knit team working on ongoing improvement of bespoke internal software platforms. The team work with agile development practices.rnrnIf this sounds like a good fit for you, please respond with an updated CV and we can discuss this in depth.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Full stack developer | contract | hampshire</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/full-stack-developer-contract-hampshire__1545218807</link>
    <description>I am currently working with a growing digital agency in Hampshire who are looking for a full stack developer to come on board for a 3-6 month contract. There is the opportunity for some remote working after the first initial weeks.rnrnYou will be primarily using Magento to develop e-commerce sites however there is the scope to use other frameworks such as Laravel and use the CMS WordPress.rnrnIf you are available or becoming available in the first few weeks of January then please reply to this email with an up to date CV and I will get back to you.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Php developer oxford £35,000 and £40,000</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-oxford-a35000-and-a40000__1545220504</link>
    <description> PHP developer opportunity with a leading media and games company based in Oxford, around a 10-15 minute walk from Oxford train station. The responsibilities of the role include designing, implementing PHP websites, applications and services, maintain and improve legacy code, create and maintain new reusable company code libraries, amongst others.rnrnThey are offering a salary of between 35,000 and 40,000, 25 days paid annual leave bank holidays, flexible working hours and a pension.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Php developer - contract - dartford</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/php-developer-contract-dartford__1545221780</link>
    <description>Avanti Recruitment key client based in Dartford is seeking several PHP Developers for a new greenfield project. You will be responsible for the production, modification and maintenance of back end applications. This involves working closely with Website Developers and designers, to ensure the website and applications are built as specified.rnrnResponsibilitiesrnrnrn	Helping to build functional requirements, technical design and implement application featuresrn	Field questions and solve problems for user support and client servicesrn	Participate in design and code reviewsrn	Integration of user-facing elements developed by the Website Developers, with server-side logicrn	Building reusable code and libraries for future usern	Optimisation of code for maximum speed and scalabilityrn	Implementation of efficient, secure and scalable softwarern	Build and maintain functional apps for the businessrn	Building and modification of API s to enable system integrationrn	Reporting on development releases monthlyrn	Solve complex scalability, platform and integration problemsrn	Be actively involved in company projects, to ensure the Development function is actively promotedrnrnrnKey Skillsrnrnrn	Candidates must be fully conversant in PHP developmentrn	Must be conversant with both object orient and procedural codingrn	Experience in Laravelrn	Candidates must be fully conversant with MySQL database design, optimisation and development (not necessarily a full DBA skillset)rn	Excellent knowledge of Integration and exchange protocols (ex. XML, Soap, Json etc.) essential.rn	A knowledge of application security is desirable (preferred experience with PCI DSS compliant systems)rn	Basic Unix command line knowledge essentialrn	Excellent knowledge of html5, CSS and JavaScript (jQuery) essentialrn	Experience working with GITrnrn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Back end developer 6 months  yorkshire and lancashire</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/back-end-developer-6-months-ayorkshire-and-lancashire__1545225138</link>
    <description>Back End Developerrnrn rnrnLocation:  Yorkshire and LancashirernrnStart Date:   Likely to be a January StartrnrnDuration:   6 monthsrnrnDaily Rate:  Negotiablernrn rnrnJob Spec:rnrn rnrnBack End Developerrnrn rnrnWhitehall Resources are looking for an experienced Back End Developer for an initial 6 month contract in Yorkshire/ Lancashire.rnrn rnrnRole Description:rnrn- As a Software Developer you will provide the technical leadership to less experienced team of Software Developers to deliver big results, and you ll provide oversight to the products they develop.rnrn- A skilled practitioner and role model in software craftsmanship, you will be responsible for ensuring best practices are followed across the department and for guiding teams to deliver a quality product.rnrn- As a Software Engineer you will develop the products which make up our citizen and staff services.rnrn- You will be responsible for the operational stability of the products you build, and ensure the on-going robustness and resilience of those products.rnrn- You ll be confident in using open source technologies like Java and JavaScript.rnrn- You ll have experience SQL and no-SQL database applications such as Postgres, MySQL, and Mongo DB, and you should have used distributed version control systems such as Git.rnrn rnrnEssential Skills/ Experience:rnrn- Java (1.8) (including Spring Boot, Drop Wizard, Hibernate, Jersey, CXF and Maven)rnrn- Microservices and Event driven architecture.rnrn- Active/Rabbit MQ, Apache Kafka, API Gateway  Kong or any equivalentrnrn- CI tooling like Git, Gitlab CI, Jenkins, SonarQube Nexus, Artifactoryrnrn rnrnDesirable Skills/ Experience:rnrn- JavaScript (including Node.js, Express, Mongoose, Sequelize and Gulp) - Desirablernrn- AWS or Microsoft Azure experiencern</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Aws infrastructure engineer – oxfordshire – 3 month contract</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/aws-infrastructure-engineer-a-oxfordshire-a-3-month-contract__1546711906</link>
    <description>AWS Infrastructure Engineer  Oxfordshire  3 month Contract This is an initial 3 month contract (likely to be extended) based in Oxfordshire on client site. I am looking for an experience and reliable Infrastructure Engineer who can provide BAU support around AWS Infrastructure. Key Skills/Requirements:  rnrnAWS Support minimum 2 years rnGitHub  rn S3 buckets   rnOn-call so flexible working required   rnWindows   rnAzure (beneficial) rnrnIf you are interested, please send me your CV for immediate consideration.rn</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Magento Developer – Leeds - 50k DOE</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/magento-developer-a-leeds-50k-doe__1546875953</link>
    <description>Magento Developer  Leeds - 50k DOE    Up to 50k depending on experience + Great Benefits Package (see below)    Are you looking to work alongside fellow Magento Developers to build and support state of the art solutions? Want to undertake more challenging and exciting projects? If so, please read on...!   A well-established agency based in Leeds is looking for a Magento Developer to join their team ASAP. They need someone who is technically strong in back end Magento development.   My client has developed an extremely fast and reliable hosting solution for Shopware customers from the vast experience they have from hosting numerous eCommerce sites. This business requires a confident individual to provide the means to build and support automated solutions using state of the art technology.   This role offers an excellent benefits package including; 25 Days Holiday + Bank Hols, flexible working and an employee monthly incentive scheme.   Please send through your CV if you have experience with any of the following:      Magento 1 2       PHP       MySQL       SOLID Principles       DDD       MVC       Design Patterns       HTML       CSS       Agile    This job will suit technically strong Magento Developers who are feeling stagnant and aren t getting the most out of their capabilities. If you are looking to utilise your technical skill set to its fullest and improve upon your abilities further, this position will equip you with the skills and experience required to do so.   Built on a foundation of industry-leading technology, a world-class team and a scientific approach to building a truly recognisable brand, ITECCO are fast becoming the UK s most influential IT recruitment company.  </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Front End and Senior Front End Developer - Milton Keynes - £40,000-£55,000 + benefits</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/front-end-and-senior-front-end-developer-milton-keynes-a40000-a55000-benefits__1546943747</link>
    <description>Front End and Senior Front End Developer required for a leading retail company on a permanent basis in Milton Keynes. Location: Milton Keynes Salary: 40,000- 55,000 + benefits Essential:  	 	HTML 	 	 	CSS 	 	 	Javascript 	 	 	eCommerce industry experience 	 	 	Responsive design/development experience 	 	 	Agile/Scrum 	    Responsibilities:  	 	Translate the needs of users regarding the solution into a technical design, within the technical and infrastructural possibilities 	 	 	Ensure technical design, customise, prepare and test solutions for use, as well as ensure the availability for users (10-50 users) 	 	 	Strong technical skills in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Responsive Design - developing transactional Ecommerce front end web applications 	 	 	Provide insights at request or at own initiative regarding quantitative and qualitative developments by means of periodical and ad hoc reports and analyses, based on reporting guidelines 	 	 	Provide technical input/advice during the briefing and processes to other team members and to other departments or clients (Merchandising, marketing, ecommerce, etc.). 	      About the role: You will be a key person involved in the re-writing of the front end of our Website. This includes being responsible for the creation and maintenance of all HTML/CSS documents (Internet and Intranet pages, email newsletters, other online campaigns, etc.). Translate the graphical design into documents that are compliant with modern online standards and within the limitations of the different medias (our web platform, web browsers (including IE6), email client programs, user computer limitations, etc.), whilst keeping a focus on accessibility and SEO.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Front end Developer / Chippenham / Market Rates / 6 months</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/front-end-developer-chippenham-market-rates-6-months__1546944412</link>
    <description>They need someone to come in and spearhead a revamped website. It is essential that you have a good grounding across front end skills this includes:  	 	React or Angular or Similar - they are using Vue but as this is not used very often they will consider a similar framework 	 	 	JavaScripts/TypeScripts 	 	 	HTML5, CSS3, Jquery 	 	 	Experience working in an agile environment 	 </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>C# or Java Developer x2 - Oxford - £40,000-£55,000</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/c-or-java-developer-x2-oxford-a40000-a55000__1546944648</link>
    <description>C# or Java Developer required to join a leading business based in Oxford. They work with the latest cutting edge technologies on a variety of different projects. They offer fantastic career advancement plans alongside regular salary reviews. Key skills: . C#  . ASP.net . Java . Spring Boot . JUnit . Gradle or Maven</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Contract Role - Central London - PHP LARAVEL - VUEJS</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/contract-role-central-london-php-laravel-vuejs__1552644869</link>
    <description>I have just had an initial 3 Month contract (with view to extend) working with a Global Financial Agency, based in the centre of London, just come across my desk that I thought may be of interest. They are looking for an Excellent PHP - Laravel Developer with experience working with Javascript, ideally Vuejs. You will be working on a couple of projects as they build a highly collaborative and innovative team. You will be required to Design, Develop, Maintain/ Support Web and Other Applications, working with Laravel, Vue, Node and Docker amongst other technologies. On a day to day basis expect to be problem solving, developing great code, and constantly learning. Also bonus points if you have any examples of working with big data, developing API s, data visualization, UI/UX, image recognition, or AI, or experience of DevOps. They are very flexible in the way that they work and are open to 1-2 days a week remote working. The day rate is between 350 - 400 a day.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>WordPress Developer</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/wordpress-developer__1552655469</link>
    <description>The details of the role are as follows:        Wordpress Developer        Location:  Hampshire    Start Date:   ASAP    Duration:   3 Months+    Daily Rate:  Market Rate        Job Spec:      WordPress Developer required by Whitehall Resources for a 3 month initial project based in Hampshire        Job Description:    - The candidate will need to have at least 3 years experience and also had experience of using Gutenberg Experience editor (Experience of Gutenberg blocks)    - The candidate will be developing on both the backend and front end (HTML, SASS)    - JavaScript    - Advantage if they have REACT although not essential.        If this role is of interest to you please call/contact me ASAP or alternatively if you know of a colleague who may be interested in this role then please feel free to pass on this email.        Please note: Could you please send me your latest CV and preferred role type: contract, fixed term or permanent please?   </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Magento contract in Southampton</title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/magento-contract-in-southampton__1552999228</link>
    <description>Web Agency in Southampton are on a look on for Magento1 and Magento2 Developers, to help them with work on high profile and popular digital websites.   400-500 per day.  This is an initial 6 months contract based on site. However after initial period of time, they are open to discuss working from home option,  This role welcomes developer with different levels of experience, working on either Front End or Back End tech stack.  If you wish to find out more about this role, please send me your CV and i will be back in touch.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Java Developer </title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/java-developera__1553098222</link>
    <description>Role: Java Developer  Location: South Oxford Salary:  30,000 - 45,000    My client are a European leading software house with 30 years experience and have over 1,300 corporate clients ranging from the largest blue chip organisations, right down to SME s and charities.   They produce over 50 different products: websites, publications, social media content and events.    They are hiring a Java Developer to work on rapidly growing multi-tenanted Java SaaS web application.   Requirements:  	At least 1 year Java Development Experience 	Good knowledge of Java 	Good knowledge of SQL 	Understanding of web technologies including, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Ajax and JSP   Technologies you will be using:  	Java 8/ Kotlin 	HTML5, CSS3, AngularJS 	Spring, Hibernate 	REST/ SOAP web services 	MySQL  If you re interested in this role and would like to find out more please send your latest CV, desired salary and availability.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Part-Time 3 months Magento contract </title>
    <link>http://www.skillbooker.com/jobboard/jobs/view/part-time-3-months-magento-contract__1553250627</link>
    <description>I am working with a Digital Agency who are currently hiring Magento developers with any range of skills (front end, back end or both) preferably with experience in Magento 1 and Magento 2.They are a growing team working on projects for prestige and global brands.  Type: 6 months contract 3 days per week  Location: Southampton  Pay: 200 - 300 Ideally, they are looking for someone who can commit to at least 10 days a month on site but they are open to remote working after initial period of time.  They are asking for someone who can code in PHP, HTML5 and CSS, preferably with experience of Magento 1 and 2 as you will be incorporating those technologies in to Magento  and writing / editing the related back-end PHP code.</description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>